Yo, what's up?
Good afternoon, big brother.
Yukimura, what are you doing in that butler get-up?
It's part of the training that's listed in Becoming a Real Man, Volume 2.
Though my skills have not quite matured, I am devoted, sir.
Look, this has nothing to do with maturity.
You're a girl, you can't do this.
My body's simply a home for my heart, sir.
A true man can transcend biology.
Don't let anyone tell you differently.
Science determined that you're female, but the truth of your soul knows who you are.
If in your heart you long to be the man you admire, don't let that dream go.
Thank you.
I'm going to make you proud of me.
I'll never give up.
You're my inspiration.
I hope to be a man just like you someday.
Okay, I can appreciate your dedication, but the clothes don't make sense.
What's with the butler thing?
A butler represents the most capable man.
Capable of what?
Who cares? It's fine.
Girls in butler costumes are totes adorable, and you know it.
Especially pretty girls.
It's actually become kind of a popular trend lately.
Like Black Butler.
Everyone loves that, so you're instantly cool if you dress like those characters, even the girls.
Or like that Chicken Butler in Mayonnaise Show.
All girls want to be Coco no Emebaru.
I love how even though she tries to act all sophist, she can't hide how awkward she is.
And if she's pissed, everyone knows about it.
Everything she does is so sexy!
The way she manages to get covered in mayonnaise every five seconds and has to change her shirt makes me think,
oh, you want it bad, you know?
And we can know she would say yes to that.
I wish I was as cute as Maybaru.
I mean, is there anyone hotter?
So yeah, that was a good call you made, Yozara.
Yukimura in a butler suit is going to do wonders for her social life.
Great. Guess I screwed that up, too.
I'm sorry. That all went over my head.
But I'm pleased to wear the clothes I was given.
I only hope they allow me to serve you as best I can.
Right on.
Well, you have my support.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Looks like one of those boys love games.
Yes, it is.
Rika thought she'd try to sort through some of her game backlog while she can.
Are they all dude-on-dude games?
No, not at all.
There are some RPGs, some shooters, and some otomege, too.
Wait, what was that last one?
Otomege? What's that?
Where the main character is a girl and she tries to date as many boys as she can.
Uh, no.
It's, it's that game.
The Simoponome crap from before.
That looks familiar.
Is it a spin-off of Sparkling School or something?
Well, color Rika impressed.
This is the otomege version of Sparkling School Life,
where the main characters and target characters' genders are flipped.
Kind of the girl version.
They call it Girl School for short.
Ugh, there are all kinds of crazy games in this world, aren't there?
Why does Rika get the feeling you're not interested?
Oh, because I'm not.
You said it's related to that crap game, and I'm sure it's just as trashy.
That's it, we're in a fight.
Look, I've never played Girl School,
but neither have you when you're practically peeing all over Sparkling School's little sister.
Which means you may as well be peeing all over my little sister.
That's fine, I hope you're happy having peed all over Kobito.
Except Kobito's not your sister.
Not the point.
I don't think it's right for you to decide you don't like it when you haven't played it yet.
So you're on their side?
Fine, I'll decide I hate it after I've played it, and I will hate it.
But then you'll have to accept that it sucks.
Hmm.
Sparkling School Life, Girls' Version 4.
Why are you skipping the opening? That's one of the best parts!
Because it's lame.
What?
I have to pick a name?
Just use your real name. That's what everyone else does. Makes it more real.
But the main character's some tramp who's trying to get with a bunch of guys.
Why would I want to be that? It'd be way better to play with meat's name.
Oh, ha-ha! You're so funny!
It's fun to play the wild girl, but you can also be the nice one and limit yourself to one guy.
It would be fun to see one of them take your V-card.
Well, that doesn't seem that bad, I guess.
Your name is Yohechiburake!
Weirdest name in the world for the weirdest girl in the world!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
She must still be bitter about the whole Simoponome thing.
I'm so freaking brilliant!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's not that funny.
What?
Why are you sabotaging Rika's efforts to spread the gospel of girl school?
All you're doing is turning others away from her tribe.
Oh, I just thought it was a funny name.
Why would you do that?
Because I, uh, look, I said I was sorry.
Rika's not asking you to apologize.
She just wants to know why you would do something wicked like that.
She's asking you nicely.
Girls are scary.
My name is Yozara Makazuki.
Starting today, I'm a high school freshman here at Sparkling Academy.
Ah, the spring breeze feels so nice.
Spring breeze?
Even though I'm just an average everyday student,
nothing would make me happier than having an exciting school life.
My breasts are heaving with hope as I make my way through the gates laden with cherry blossoms.
Did you just see your breasts are heaving with hope?
Hey, that was cheesy, but you don't have breasts.
That wasn't very spring breezy of you.
I'll kill you.
Calm down, heckling is part of gaming.
Ouch.
I'm sorry, I was daydreaming.
Here, can you stand?
Well, that was nice. Who is this boy?
Oji Shinomori, he's a star freshman just like your character.
He's the heir to the Shinomori conglomerate,
which means every girl in school wants to be with him.
Nice to meet you.
I'm hoping this year will be great for both of us.
That boy was really cool.
If I already met someone like him on my first day,
then the rest of the year is looking sweet as roses.
What a sweet, rosy-red year you have ahead of you.
Okay, I'm gonna let you pick which name do you like better,
rosy or spring breezy.
I am not using my name on the flower bed for brains, idiot.
How do I switch it back to the other one?
Whoa, it's just a game.
The dialogue is the same no matter who's playing.
Oh, hey.
So, like, how do you know Shinomori?
Who the hell is this random hag?
Yoko sits next to the player in class.
Refer to her with questions about other students.
Um, I think I'll refer to her with my fist instead.
She's a bit of an a-hole.
She was being nice!
Yeah, way too soon.
You don't walk up to a random stranger and act like your besties.
That is a cocky, punk-ass move.
She's just like Akari.
What's your deal?
Akari's like the sweetest girl in the world.
I like you, Yozara.
Let's be friends, okay?
Sure.
It's nice to meet you.
She is so fake.
She's so gonna stab me in the back.
I just know it.
Low scores in all areas except sleeping?
Loser.
Guess I'll build up her grades first.
That's better.
Almost done.
Hmm.
This question's a hard one.
Oh, shut up.
You're never gonna make it anywhere
if you can't get through level one freshman homework.
Man, I hate this game.
It's not challenging.
You look like you're having trouble.
Want me to explain that to you?
Hi, boy with glasses!
Ah!
Is that like the girl's school version of Yukiko?
That dude kind of sucks.
His name is Tomo Suzutsuki.
He has the highest GPA in the class.
Oh, well, that's cool.
He can help you with homework, right?
Great.
So I think it's great that you study in the library in your free time.
And I can't stop thinking about you.
What?
What does that mean?
He may look like a smart guy, but he's actually just a huge perv.
Get out of the way.
I'm busy.
I admire you for wanting to solve such a difficult problem on your own.
However, there's nothing wrong with asking for help once in a while.
The greatest minds do it.
Please don't hesitate to call if you change your mind.
Does anybody else find him annoying?
Guess I'm gonna have to find somewhere else to study besides the library.
Yes!
Now that's more like me.
Yeah, but it's a dating game and you killed your social skills.
Rika finds it painful to watch someone fail so miserably this way.
She wants to cry.
Even in games, she's a tragic mess.
Really?
You punks must have a death wish if you're coming after me when I have a strength level of 380.
Take this!
What the crap?
Come on!
Why isn't the attack button working?
I think you're confused as to what kind of game this is.
I'm gonna be honest.
Guys like you seriously make me want to puke.
Bastard.
Get him!
You're Yozora Mikazuki, right?
How do you know my name?
You are famous, you know.
The name's Eiji Nagatani.
This ain't the place for elite types like you to be wandering around.
You should go home.
Maybe I should ask him out.
You should!
But does that mean this type of guy is your type?
Of course not.
I'm just trying to make this game more interesting since you're forcing me to play.
So shut up.
Guys like that creep me out with their messy hair, crazy eyes, and boring voices.
They're also extremely rude.
Oh, shut up!
You haven't even heard to talk.
Huh?
You mean next Sunday?
Right.
Let's meet...
Um, how about the batting cages?
Sure.
That's fine, I guess.
Okay, it's a date.
Seriously?
Wonderful, Tina.
Let's go.
Wow, you're pretty good.
Anyone can do this much.
You did your hair different today, huh?
Hmm? Did you say something?
Huh? It was nothing.
Wow. He's actually pretty observant for a commoner.
I'm impressed.
Maybe Kotika would benefit from taking some lessons from that guy.
Lessons in what?
Noticing girls' hairstyles.
When they take the time to do something different with their hair,
you should mention it and follow that with a compliment.
I do that anyway. Ask Yozara.
When you cut your hair, I said it looked nice, right?
I don't remember. Why would you bring that up now?
So you complimented Yozara's hair. Rika gets it.
And while we're on the subject,
I noticed you've been changing yours around a lot later.
Did you notice this whole time and never said anything?
You never once reacted, so Rika was afraid
that she was as memorable as a rock on the roadside.
She has lost many nights of sleep and suffers massive depression
because you're stupid!
I'm sorry. Chill out.
It's just there's never a time I'm not watching you.
Commenting would get old.
I can't let you out of my side or you'll blow something up.
It's way too late to win Rika over with that line of crap.
Maybe if you'd worked on your status this whole time.
Status of what? What do you mean?
I mean if you'd spent a little more time building your affection points with Rika,
you'd be going at it with her right now in a loud, passionate cacophony of pleasure.
As it is, your points are very low and she cannot credit you for this mild excuse for a compliment.
If you bring those points up, you'll get yourself up!
But why should I have to win affection points from you? We're friends.
Because I said so!
Uh, wait. Let's talk about this.
Rika is hurt and needs to be alone to practice some self-love.
Okay, thanks, bye.
Uh, what does she mean by self-love?
Exactly what you think. Rika's a pervert.
Another fun day, huh?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Uh, what is happening here?
I don't want to be presumptuous, but he seems nervous like he might like me.
Well, there are definitely feelings going on over there.
So then yes, he does like me?
Listen, Yozara, I think we should stop seeing each other.
What?
I mean, you're like the school superstar.
Shoot, they even made you student body president.
You keep hanging out with a punk like me.
It'll destroy your reputation.
You are such a wuss.
Who cares what other people decide to think of me?
I'll decide who I want to be with, do you understand?
So you have to stay with me!
I never saw it coming, but I actually feel sorry for Yozara.
Me too.
If she keeps playing, maybe, maybe they'll make up.
I got into a first-rate university, but I didn't manage to get close to anyone.
It was a lonely three years.
It was my own fault.
I should have tried harder to make friends.
That was the worst ending ever!
What's going to happen to Eiji now?
Rika is afraid at some point you must have failed to clear a key checkpoint.
You were never seen interacting with any of the other boys, or even Yoko for that matter.
Oh, yeah.
Don't get too down on yourself about it. That's what's great about gaming.
You can learn from your mistakes and try again.
Next time, you can come on to them hardcore and play the Vixen.
Yeah, no thanks. I'm over it.
If this is what happens when I get to choose how I live my life, that's fine.
But I am sorry that I called it a crappy game.
Girl school was actually fun. I didn't expect that.
Oh, and P.S.
I can barely stand the pansy core guys in my real life.
I don't need to create more in a game.
Hey guys, what's up?
Good morning, Kotika. How are you doing today?
I'm good. You changed your hairstyle, didn't you?
That's all you got?
What do you want from me? I noticed you changed your hair, didn't I?
You did, but what did Rika change about it?
Was it the way she's wearing it, or the color, or did she cut some inches off?
Or maybe it's all three.
Did you trim it a bit?
This is more than a trim!
I know, gosh. I was just kidding. Give me a second.
Oh, you're a tricky one. You had Rika going.
You bought some new hair tops.
It's more than that, jerk!
Okay, Spill It, what's with the bimbo look?
You over being smart?
Absolutely not.
Rika just wanted to experiment with color.
That's bad for your hair, you know.
Not to worry.
Rika used a hair dye formula she created all by herself.
You made it?
Rika is quite proud of this one.
There is almost zero fading or risk of damage in this formula.
And the most amazing feature is you can switch back to your natural color anytime you decide to.
Isn't that awesome?
Yeah, I guess it's kind of awesome.
But if I'm being totally honest, your inventions lately, they're not blowing me away.
Like which ones?
Well, computer software, long-lasting light bulbs, electric pots that boil water without a heat source,
automatic beetle-raising tanks, ice cream without calories, and now reversible hair dye.
I mean, don't get me wrong, they're all very useful products, but where's the sparkle? Where's the romance?
Ryan, what kind of invention do you want from Rika?
Well, I never thought about it.
Oh, I know. How about one of those giant robots you like?
That's a national government-level project! It'd take Rika years to get that approved!
Oh, then how about a fifth-dimensional pocket?
The difficulty level on that one far exceeds your robot idea.
All right, then. Maybe a flashlight that can make things bigger or smaller.
Or maybe like a cloth, and you can wrap it around broken items to fix them.
Or a jelly you can eat and understand any language you want.
Do they make those yet?
No, scratch that. How do you feel about time machines?
What?
Ladies and gentlemen, Rika gives you time machine!
Huh? That's a time machine?
Can you go to both the past and the future with it?
Unfortunately, there's no future mode. Travelers may only visit their past.
You're kidding, right?
If you don't believe Rika, put it on and try it yourself!
Now, don't freak out in there. Rika will bring you back after five minutes.
Um, okay.
Be careful.
Have you ever tested that thing to make sure it's safe?
Rika is a mad scientist! You have nothing to worry about!
Yeah, the word mad isn't very reassuring.
Don't sweat the small stuff, Kotaka.
Now, Rika needs you to concentrate and think of what part of your past you want to revisit.
I know exactly where I want to go.
No way. That's amazing.
What are you mumbling about over there?
Uh...
Hmm.
Wow. It's really hurt.
What's going on, Taka?
Huh? But I... uh...
Are you having a seizure?
No, I'm fine. It was just some gas.
You're so weird.
All right, well, don't forget tomorrow. I gotta go home now.
I can't believe it worked. I'm in that exact day.
Have a good night, Taka.
Yozura, wait!
How do you know what my real name is?
Listen, my family and I are moving day after tomorrow. I won't be back for around ten years.
So that means tomorrow will be my last chance to see you.
Really?
I'm sorry.
For leaving you alone.
But we'll stay friends, even if we don't see each other anymore.
Except you forgot about her until you came back.
No matter what, I promise I'll never forget you.
And then you couldn't even place her face once you did.
I'm sorry. I really am.
And I always will be. Very sorry.
Not good enough.
I'll never forgive you for that!
Die!
Ah!
I am the demon Astero!
What the?
You'll never expect me now, Koraka!
Please forgive me!
Yozura!
It's all over. Are you okay?
So weird. I forgot. You only left me there for five minutes. It felt like so much longer.
Rika owes you an apology. She lied when she said it was a time machine. It's not.
It's actually a kind of sleep aid that Rika created to give a hypnotic effect to the sleeper so they could dream about whatever they wanted simply by wishing hard enough for it.
So wait, that was just... a dream?
Rika only wanted to pull a little prank on you, but it sounded like she ended up giving you a terrible nightmare instead.
She is very sorry for her actions.
Hey, don't be. I'm sorry for criticizing your inventions. It was never my place.
That time machine's brilliant. You should be proud.
Sure, things got weird at the end, but I really did feel like I was time traveling. It was so awesome.
Most of all, you allowed me to tell her what I didn't before, even if it was all a dream.
Rika is happy. That means you did get to time travel with dreams as your portal.
Yeah. I went back ten years.
Oh. Are you sure it was that far back?
Okay, hold on. I have a question for you.
Hmm? Yeah, shoot.
Why were you talking to Yozara in that dream? I mean, if you went back ten years.
Come with me.
Hey, Taka, isn't this cool we get to do the preview this time?
Things got weird ten years into our future, didn't they?
I wonder what'll happen next.
Well, we say the title of the next episode,
Unbreakable Strange Girl.
That sounds awful.
Couldn't they come up with something more appealing?
I wonder which girl they think is unbreakable and strange.
I'm guessing you.
I've never done a strange thing in my whole life!
I think dressing like a boy and picking on people
for no reason counts as strange.
That was way harsh, Taka.
So child talk now?
Yeah.
It is probably not you it.
Okay, my hand is up.
Taka.
Yes, four side asks this word.
I'll hold the apple to tierra.
But how can it seem to be if they're dai- doświad when it's gonna Engine.
And it doesn't seem to t'all.
I don't see yet.
I'm using Buddy talking to them.
donde' everybody Miller can use to drive through it.
And of course it seems to be complicated.
Let's do this thing.
What about next May we?